已经没有帝国了 曼达人
The Empire is gone, Mando.
《曼达洛人》前情提要
它对我至关重要
This asset was of extreme importance to me.
我得要保证我能拿到它
I had to ensure its delivery.
他不是地方上的军阀
He's not a local warlord.
他是帝国的
He's Imperial.
那我来
I'm in.
我们的隐秘让我们得以生存
Our secrecy is our survival.
我们的生存让我们拥有力量
Our survival is our strength.
从前我们的力量来自于我们的数量
Our strength was once in our numbers.
现在我们不见天日地苟且
Now, we live in the shadows.
我们的世界被帝国给粉碎了
Our world was shattered by the Empire.
你得把神秘人物转移了
You're going to have to relocate the covert.
此乃正道
This is the way.
你们捣毁了那里之后 它被丢下了
In the wake of your destruction, it was left behind.
它还是猎手吗
Is it still a hunter?
不 但它会保护
No. But it will protect.
你对机器人还真有偏见 是吧
You got a real thing for droids, don't you?
我只是对那个机器人有偏见
I got a real thing for that droid.
让我带孩子去见他...
Let me take the child to him...
我们杀了他 离开这里
Let's just kill him and get out of here.
我们都想干掉客户
We both need the client to be eliminated.
他说得对
He's right.
只要帝国人还活着 他就会派猎人追杀那个孩子
As long as the Imp lives, he'll send hunters after the child.
这是陷阱
It's a trap.
他们把孩子带来了吗 带来了
Have they brought the child? Yes, they have.
你们有我想要的东西
You have something I want.
奎尔 你在吗
Kuiil? Are you there?
再过一会儿...
In a few moments...
奎尔 在吗
Kuiil! Are you there?
它就是我的了
...it will be mine.
星球大战
飞行摩托携带目标已经抵达哨卡
Speeder bikes have arrived at the checkpoint with the asset.
等待确认
Awaiting confirmation.
别出声
Knock it off!
是否继续进城 等待确认
Waiting for confirmation to continue into town.
可以继续
That's a go to proceed,
但我建议你们再确认一下
but I advise you to doublecheck.
星区总督一落地
The Moff just touched down
就已经消灭了一队本地的士兵
and already took out a squad of local troopers.
原地待命
Standing by.
他刚刚是说吉迪恩杀了他自己的人吗
Did he just say that Gideon killed his own men?
谁知道呢
Oh, who knows?
这些家伙初到一个地方
These guys like to lay down the law
总喜欢给人来个下马威
when they first arrive into town.
你明白的
You know how it is.
我说了别出声
I said, shut up.
那东西到底是什么啊
What is that thing, anyway?
我也不知道
Uh, I don't know.
也许星区总督想要吃了它 我只是执行命令
Maybe Moff wants to eat it. I don't ask questions.
我能看看它吗
Can I see it?
难道你刚才没听见
Did you not just hear that
星区总督吉迪恩杀了十几个自己的兵来树军威
Moff Gideon killed a dozen of his own troopers to make a point.
行了 这军威我领教了
Okay. I get that point.
你领教了没有 领教了
Do you get the point? Yes.
那就好
Okay.
我们要不要给那东西喝点水
Should we offer that thing some water?
你就是想看看它
You just wanna look at it.
是又怎么样 你都看见了
So what? You got to see it!
就一眼
Barely.
我把它从地上抓起来
I mean, I grabbed it up off the ground
往包里一塞
and I stuffed it in the sack.
那也比我看见的多啊
It's more than I got to see it.
在亲手交给星区总督之前
Look, I'm not taking it out of this bag
我是不会把它从包里拿出来的
until I deliver it to the Moff.
好吧 行了 别再问了
Fine. Okay. Stop asking.
我来问问 太傻了
Let me check on this thing. This is crazy.
有什么进展吗
Any update yet?
没有 仍然在等待确认
That's a negative. Still waiting on confirmation.
他刚刚杀了个军官 因为他打断了他
He just killed an officer for interrupting him,
因此恐怕还要等一阵子
so this might take a while.
谢谢
Thank you.
继续原地待命 真难以置信
Standing by still. Unbelievable.
那东西有多久没动了
Hey, how long has it been since that thing moved?
不知道 一两分钟吧 别担心
I don't know, like a minute or two. Don't worry.
可远不止一分钟了
Uh, it's been way longer than a minute.
我的天啊
oh, my god.
难道我们不得看看它是不是还活着吗
Shouldn't we check and see if it's still alive?
你那下打得挺狠的
You hit it pretty hard.
你就是想看看它
You just wanna see it.
我们应该看看它是不是受伤了
We should check and see if it's hurt.
你绝对不希望把袋子交给吉迪恩
The last thing that you want is to give Gideon a bag
而他打开以后发现里面的东西死了吧...
and have him open it and find whatever is dead...
好好好 给你看 怎么样
Okay. Okay, look. Here you go. See?
看一眼 好好的呢
Take a peek. Everything's fine.
那是什么
What is that?
我不知道 宠物之类的吧
I don't know. It's a pet or something.
宠物 你不是说...
A pet? I thought you...
活该
Serves you right.
住手
Stop that.
来者何人
Identify yourself!
我是IG11
I am IG11.
我是这孩子的机器人护理
I am this child's nurse droid
我要求你们立即把他交还给我
and require that you remand him to me immediately.
机器人护理
A nurse droid?
我还以为是猎手 IG机器人不都是猎手吗
I thought it was a hunter. Aren't IGs usually hunters?
很显然这个是护理
Yeah, well, evidently this one's a nurse.
对不起护理 但你得离开这
I'm sorry, nurse, but you're gonna have to get out of here.
你是违抗我的要求吗
Are you refusing my request?
不
No.
我是命令你离开这
I'm telling you to get out of here.
那场面可不太愉快
That was unpleasant.
抱歉让你看见了
I'm sorry you had to see that.
曼达洛人
第一季 第八集[季终]
复仇
还有别的出口吗
Is there another way out?
没有 只有这个
No, that's it.
下水道呢 下水道
What about the sewers? Sewers?
曼达洛人在下水道里有个隐蔽所
The Mandalorians have a covert down in the sewers.
如果我们能下去 他们就能帮我们逃跑
If we can get down there, they can help us escape.
下水道很好
Yeah, sewers are good.
查找入口
Checking for access points.
他们在等什么
What the hell are they waiting for?
等等
Hold up.
他们在架设EWeb重型连发炮
They're setting up an EWeb.
完了
It's over.
我找到下水道口了
I found the sewer vent.
我们赶紧离开这里吧
Let's get the hell out of here.
组装完成 你们还要拆多久
It's assembled! How long until that thing's cleared?
轰开 我没子弹了
Blow it. I'm out of charges.
让开
Get out of the way!
你们这么惊慌就表示
Your astute panic suggests
你了解你现在的处境
that you understand your situation.
我希望避免任何进一步的暴力
I would prefer to avoid any further violence,
提议大家考虑一下现状
and encourage a moment of consideration.
我的随行人员已经完成
Members of my escort have completed assembly
一个EWeb重型连发炮的组装
of an EWeb heavy repeating blaster.
暴风军常用武器 是一种速射激光炮
如果你不熟悉这种武器
If you are unfamiliar with this weapon,
我确信共和国震击兵
I am sure that Republican Shock Trooper
来自阿尔德兰的卡拉·辛西娅·杜恩
Cara Synthia Dune of Alderaan
会告诉你她见证了
will advise you that she has witnessed
和她同级的其他人在面对这个型号的
many of her ranks vaporize middescent
上一代是如何被轰得所剩无几
facing the predecessor of this particular model.
或者退役的曼达洛猎人丁·贾林
Or perhaps the decommissioned Mandalorian hunter, Din Djarin,
听见了曼达洛围攻的歌
has heard the songs of the Siege of Mandalore,
以下均指《克隆人战争》中的曼达洛围攻一役
当炮艇装备了类似的武器
when gunships outfitted with similar ordnance
此战役中 绝地武士来曼达洛星球击杀达斯·摩尔
在千泪之夜中
laid waste to fields of Mandalorian recruits
共和国出兵进攻曼达洛
把杀死无数曼达洛士兵
in The Night of a Thousand Tears.
我建议叛变的地方官格里夫·卡尔加
I advise disgraced Magistrate Greef Karga
回顾他人生中积累的智慧
to search the wisdom of his years
并敦促你放下武器走出来
and urge you to lay down your arms and come outside.
你被困的建筑将在短时间内被夷为平地
The structure you are trapped in will be razed in short order
你的传奇人生将会有一个随便的结尾
and your storied lives will come to an unceremonious end.
你有什么建议
What do you propose?
合理的谈判
Reasonable negotiation.
你提供什么保证
What assurance do you offer?
如果你问你能否信任我 你不能
If you're asking if you can trust me, you cannot.
就像你背叛了我们的交易一样
Just as you betrayed our business arrangement,
我很乐于违背任何承诺 看着你死在我手里
I would gladly break any promise and watch you die at my hand.
我做出的保证如下 我会为自身利益行动
The assurance I give is this: I will act in my own selfinterest,
此刻这需要你们的合作 也代表你们的利益
which at this time involves your cooperation and benefit.
我给你到天黑的时间思考
I will give you until nightfall,
然后我会让EWeb枪扫射
and then I will have the EWeb cannon open fire.
我觉得我听明白了
I say we hear him out.
我们一开门就会死
The minute we open that door, we're dead.
不开门也是死
We're dead if we don't.
至少在外面 我们有机会
At least out there, we've got a shot.
你说起来容易
That's easy for you to say.
我是义军突击士兵
I'm a Rebel Shock Trooper.
他们会把我送给"夺心魔"
They'll upload me to a Mind Flayer.
本省出自于《龙与地牢》 可能是指类似波尔古雷[侠盗一号中提及]这种可以读心的生物
那些不是真的 那只是战时的宣传
Those aren't real. That was just wartime propaganda.
我不想知道 我要杀出一条路
I don't care to find out. I'm shooting my way out of here.
你呢 曼达人
What about you, Mando?
我知道他是谁
I know who he is.
我是马夫·吉迪恩
It's Moff Gideon.
不
No.
马夫·吉迪恩因战争罪被处决
Moff Gideon was executed for war crimes.
就是他 他知道我的名字
It's him. He knew my name.
所以呢 这证明了什么
So? What does that prove?
从我孩童时起 就没人提起这个名字了
I haven't heard that name spoken since I was a child.
在曼达洛星球上吗
On Mandalore?
我不是在曼达洛上出生的
I was not born on Mandalore.
但你是曼达洛人
But you're a Mandalorian.
曼达洛人不是一个种族
Mandalorian isn't a race.
这是一种信条
It's a creed.
我是个弃婴
I was a foundling.
他们在战斗部队把我养大
They raised me in the Fighting Corps.
我被当作他们的一员
I was treated as one of their own.
当我长大了 我就宣誓信条
When I came of age, I was sworn to the Creed.
我唯一的姓氏记录
The only record of my family name
只有在曼达洛的登记记录上才有
was in the registers of Mandalore.
马夫·吉迪恩在大清洗期间是帝国安全局的官员
Moff Gideon was an ISB Officer during the purge.
所以我才知道是他
That's how I know it's him.
所以他才知道我们都是谁
That's how he knows who we all are.
他说他需要我们
He says he needs us,
这意味着孩子安全地逃走了
which means the child got away safely.
当乌格瑙特人没有回应的时候我很担心
I was worried when the Ugnaught didn't respond,
但如果他们抓住了那孩子 我们早就死了
but if they'd captured the kid, we'd already be dead.
再呼叫他们一次
Hail them again.
回话 奎尔
Come in, Kuiil.
奎尔
Kuiil?
没有回应 他们可能屏蔽了信号
Nothing. They might have jammed the link.
奎尔已经被击杀了
Kuiil has been terminated.
你做了什么
What did you do?
我正在履行我的基本职能
I am fulfilling my base function.
是什么
Which is?
护理和保护
To nurse and protect.
那是什么
What was that?
看起来是活物
Look alive.
看
Look!
掩护我
Cover me.
用火把他们烧出来
Burn them out.
坚持住 伙计 我们会把你带出去的
Stay with me, buddy. We're gonna get you out of here.
这是我们唯一的出路 你能把它弄开吗
This is our only path out. Can you clear it?
坚持住
Stay with me.
如果你靠近这个孩子
If you go near this child,
我别无选择 只能杀了你
I will no choice but to kill you.
我理解 你能把栅栏移开吗
I understand. Can you do anything to move the grate?
当然可以
Yes, of course.
我喜欢IG机器人
Oh, I love IG units.
我不行了 去吧
I'm not gonna make it. Go.
闭嘴 你只是头被打晕了 你会没事的
Shut up. You just got your bell rung. You'll be fine.
别管我
Leave me.
我得把这东西摘了
I'm gonna need to take this thing off.
不 别管我
No. You leave me.
你要确保孩子安全
You make sure the child is safe.
拿着
Here.
当你到了曼达洛人的藏身点 你就给他们看
When you get to the Mandalorian covert, you show them that.
你告诉他们是丁·贾林的
You tell them it's from Din Djarin.
你告诉他们弃婴是由我保护的
You tell them the foundling was in my protection,
他们就会帮你
and they'll help you.
我们能做到的
We can make it.
快点 走吧
Come on! Let's go!
我不行了 你知道的
I'm not gonna make it and you know it.
你保护孩子
You protect the child.
我可以尽力拖延住他们 足够让你逃走
I can hold them back long enough for you to escape.
让我以战士应有的方式死去
Let me have a warrior's death.
我不会丢下你的
I won't leave you.
此乃正道
This is the way.
快点 门开了 我们走
Come on! It's open, let's go!
去吧 快走
Go. Go.
我们得走了 立刻
We have to move! Now!
去吧
Go.
逃走并保护这个孩子
Escape and protect this child.
我会和曼达洛人待在一起
I will stay with the Mandalorian.
答应我 你会带上他
Promise me you'll bring him.
我保证
You have my word.
动手吧
Do it.
动什么手
Do what?
赶紧结束吧
Just get it over with.
与其被帝国杀死 我更希望死在你手下
I'd rather you kill me than some Imp.
我告诉过你 我已经不是猎人了
I told you. I am no longer a hunter.
我是医护机器人
I am a nurse droid.
所有的IG机器人都是猎人
IGs are all hunters.
我不是 我的程序被重写过
Not this one. I was reprogrammed.
如果要救你 我得先取下你的头盔
I need to remove your helmet if I am to save you.
你试试看 我会杀了你
Try it and I'll kill you.
这是禁令
It is forbidden.
在我发誓严守信条之后
No living thing has seen me without my helmet
没有活物见过头盔下的我
since I swore the Creed.
我不是生物
I am not a living thing.
这是巴克塔喷雾 几小时内就可以治愈你
This is a bacta spray. It will heal you in a matter of hours.
你的中央处理系统受到了伤害
You have suffered damage to your central processing unit.
你是指我的脑部
You mean my brain?
那是个笑话 想让你放松一下
That was a joke. It is meant to put you at ease.
我来扶你
I got you.
你知道该走哪条路吗
Do you know which way to go?
不 我不了解这些隧道
No. I don't know these tunnels.
我只从集市进来过
I've only entered from the bazaar.
如果跟着硫磺的气味走
Well, if we get the smell of sulfur and we follow it,
就会带我们到河流流经的的平原
it'll lead us up to the plains where the river flows.
帝国会在我们赶到飞船之前就杀了我们
And the Imps will catch us before we make it to the ship.
我们需要曼达洛人护送我们到安全的地方
We need the Mandalorians to escort us to safety.
这地方就像迷宫一样
Ugh, this place is a maze.
停下
Stop.
我可以站立了
I can stand.
巴克塔喷雾起效了
The bacta infusion is working.
我去找路
I'll try to find tracks.
我们快到了
We're close.
在这转弯
Turn here.
我们该走了
We should go.
你们走吧 开走飞船
You go. Take the ship.
我不能就这么离开
I can't leave it this way.
你知道这件事吗
Did you know about this?
这是你赏金猎人的杰作吗
Is this the work of your bounty hunters?
不
No.
当你拿上赏金 离开系统 战斗就结束了
When you left the system and took the prize, the fighting ended
那些猎人就会自行消失
and the hunters just melted away.
你知道是怎么回事
You know how it is.
他们是雇佣军 不是狂徒
They're mercenaries. They're not zealots.
是不是你干的 是不是
Did you do this? Did you?
不 那不是他的错
No! It was not his fault.
是我们自己暴露了
We revealed ourselves.
我们早就知道离开藏身处之后会发生什么
We knew what could happen if we left the covert.
帝国不久之后就赶到了
The Imperials arrived shortly thereafter.
这就是结局
This is what resulted.
有人活下来了吗
Did any survive?
我希望如此 有些人可能已经逃离了星球
I hope so. Some may have escaped offworld.
和我们一起走
Come with us.
不
No.
在我回收完这些废墟之前 我不会离开这个地方
I will not abandon this place until I have salvaged what remains.
让我看看 到底为了保护谁的安全才造成了这种破坏
Show me the one whose safety deemed such destruction.
就是它
This is the one.
你先去猎杀它 然后又救了它
This is the one that you hunted, then saved?
没错 它也救过我
Yes. The one that saved me as well.
泥角兽 没错
From the mudhorn? Yes.
它看上去挺没用的
It looks helpless.
它受伤了 但它并非无用
It's injured, but it is not helpless.
它的种族可以通过意念移动物体
Its species can move objects with its mind.
我知道这种事
I know of such things.
万古之前的诗歌中
The songs of eons past tell of battles
记载了曼达洛大帝
between Mandalore The Great,
和一个叫绝地武士的巫师教团之间的战争
and an order of sorcerers called Jedi
运用这种力量进行战斗
that fought with such powers.
它是敌人吗
It is an enemy?
不 它的族人是 但它不是
No. Its kind were enemies, but this individual is not.
那它是什么
What is it?
它是弃婴
It is a foundling.
根据信条 你得负责照顾它
By Creed, it is in your care.
你希望我训练它
You wish me to train this thing?
它太虚弱了 会死的
It is too weak. It would die.
你别无选择 必须让它和族人团聚
You have no choice. You must reunite it with its own kind.
在哪里
Where?
你必须自己确定
This, you must determine.
你希望我在整个星系中找到它的家
You expect me to search the galaxy for the home of this creature
还要把他送回敌对的巫师族
and deliver it to a race of enemy sorcerers?
此乃正道
This is the Way.
几分钟之内 帝国人就会冲进这些隧道
These tunnels will be lousy with Imps in a matter of minutes.
我们至少应该讨论一下逃脱计划
We should at least discuss an escape plan.
如果你顺着下降的隧道走
If you follow the descending tunnel,
就会到达地下河
it will lead you to the underground river.
河会向下流到熔岩平原上
It flows downstream toward the lava flats.
我们该走了
I think we should go.
我留下
I'm staying.
我得帮她 而且我需要康复
I need to help her and I need to heal.
你必须走了
You must go.
你得照顾这个弃婴
A foundling is in your care.
根据信条 直到它成年 或是和族人团聚之前
By Creed, until it is of age or reunited with its own kind,
你如同它父亲
you are as its father.
此乃正道
This is the Way.
你已经赢得了印记
You have earned your Signet.
你们是两个人的家族
You are a clan of two.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我会光荣地戴上这枚印记
I will wear this with honor.
我们该走了
We should go.
IG机器人 请守好外面的走廊
IG, please guard the outer hallway.
有一队侦察兵正在逼近
A scouting party draws near.
等等 我不太会照顾孩子
Hang on. I don't do the baby thing.
我还为你的行程准备了一份礼物
I have one more gift for your journey.
你在浴火之凤中训练过吗
Have you trained in the Rising Phoenix?
是的 在我小时候
When I was a boy. Yes.
这会让你更完整
Then this will make you complete.
谢谢
Thank you.
等你康复后 就得开始进行训练
When you have healed, you will begin your drills.
在你掌握之前 它不会服从你的命令
Until you know it, it will not listen to your commands.
我明白
I understand.
你们安全了
You are protected.
还会有更多人来 你必须走了
More will come. You must go.
和我们一起走
Come with us.
这里是我的地盘
My place is here.
补充你们的弹药
Restock your munitions.
IG 替丁·贾林拿着 直到他能穿为止
IG, carry this for Din Djarin until he is well enough to wear it.
走吧
Now, go.
顺河流直下 穿过平原
Down to the river and across the plains.
一路顺风
Be safe on your journey.
谢谢
Thank you.
曼达人
Hey, mando.
他们在哪里
Where are they?
问你呢 他们在哪里
I said, where are they?
这是熔岩河
This is the lava river.
渡轮机器人被坏了
The ferry droid is fried.
嗯 但是如果我们把船推出去
Yeah, but if we push the boat out,
就可以让它顺流而下
we can get it to float downstream.
来吧
Come on.
看上去很旧 能承受高温吗
Looks old. Will it take the heat?
你有更好的主意吗
You got a better idea?
好像没有
Guess not.
用力
Push!
快点 你在干什么
Come on! What're you doing?
试试这个 用力
Let's try this. Push!
你们能让开吗
You guys mind getting out of the way?
干得好
Good job.
小心脚 这是熔岩
Watch your feet. It's molten lava.
可不嘛
No kidding.
这里没人能和机器人沟通吧
I don't suppose anybody here speaks droid?
他应该在问我们想去哪里
I believe he is asking where we would like to go.
顺流而下 去熔岩滩
Down river. To the lava flat.
到了 我们自由了
That's it. We're free!
不
No.
不 我们没有
No, we're not.
暴风兵 他们在隧道口的两侧
Stormtroopers. They're flanking the mouth of the tunnel.
看起来有一整排 他们知道我们要出去
It looks like an entire platoon. They must know we're coming.
停船
Stop the boat.
机器人 我说了停船
Hey, Droid, I said stop the boat.
我在和你说话
Hey! I'm talking to you.
我说了停船
I said stop!
我们还在移动
We're still moving.
看来必须得动手了
Looks like we fight.
他们人太多了
There are too many.
那你有什么建议 我不能投降
Then what do you suggest? 'Cause I can't surrender.
他们的目标只有这个孩子
They will not be satisfied with anything less than the child.
这是不能接受的
This is unacceptable.
我来消灭敌人 你赶紧逃
I will eliminate the enemy and you will escape.
你没有这种火力 伙计
You don't have that kind of firepower, pal.
你撑不到出口的
You wouldn't even get to daylight.
这不是我的目标
That is not my objective.
快到了 准备好
We're getting close. Saddle up.
我还有制造商的安全协议
I still have the security protocols from my manufacturer.
如果我的设计遭到破坏 就必须自毁
If my designs are compromised, I must selfdestruct.
你在说什么
What're you talking about?
我不能被抓 我必须被摧毁
I am not permitted to be captured. I must be destroyed.
我们是要吵架 还是逃出这里
Are we gonna keep talking, or get out of here?
我不能再帮你拿这个了
I can no longer carry this for you.
我也无法照看孩子了
Nor can I watch over the child.
等等 你不能自毁
Wait. You can't selfdestruct.
你的基本指令是照看孩子
Your base command is to watch the child.
这个高于你们制造商的协议 对吧
That supersedes your manufacturer's protocol, right?
对吧 正确
Right? This is correct.
很好 拿上爆能枪
Good. Now, grab a blaster
帮我们冲出去
and help us shoot our way out.
通过战斗取胜是不可能的
Victory through combat is impossible.
我们会被抓 孩子会被抢走
We will be captured. The child will be lost.
很可惜 如果想保住孩子
Sadly, there is no scenario where the child is saved,
就必须牺牲我
in which I survive.
你老实待着
Listen, you're not going anywhere.
我们需要你 让我们想一个
We need you. Let's just come up with a...
请告诉我 你会好好照顾这个孩子
Please tell me the child will be safe in your care.
只要你答应我 我就可以启动辅助指令
If you do so, I can default to my secondary command.
但你会被毁灭的
But you'll be destroyed.
这样你就活下来了 我也完成了我的使命
And you will live, and I will have served my purpose.
不 我们需要你
No. We need you.
没什么可难过的 我又不是人
There is nothing to be sad about. I have never been alive.
我不难过
I'm not sad.
你很难过 我是护士机器人 我分析了你的声音
Yes, you are. I'm a nurse droid. I've analyzed your voice.
IG
IG?
你在干什么
What're you doing?
制造商的协议规定我不能被抓
Manufacturer's protocol dictates I cannot be captured.
我必须被毁灭
I must be destroyed.
吉迪恩星区总督
Moff Gideon!
他打偏了 下次不会了
He missed! He won't next time.
我们的爆能枪对他毫无用处
Our blasters are useless against him.
让孩子使用魔法之手吧
Let's make the baby do the magic hand thing.
宝宝 使用魔法之手
Come on, baby! Do the magic hand thing.
我没办法了 我有
I'm out of ideas. I'm not.
他来了
Here he comes!
不
No!
太厉害了 曼达人 非常厉害啊
That was impressive, Mando. Very impressive.
你的公会佣金价好像上升了
It looks like your Guild rates have just gone up.
还有暴风兵吗
Any more stormtroopers?
这个城镇应该没有了
I think we cleaned up the town.
我想待一段时间 以防万一
I'm thinking of staying around just to be sure.
你要留在这里 有何不可
You're staying here? Well, why not?
尼瓦罗是一颗非常美丽的星球
Nevarro is a very fine planet.
现在糟粕和罪恶已被洗净
And now that the scum and villainy have been washed away,
它又恢复辉煌了
it's very respectable again.
作为赏金猎人的老巢吗
As a bounty hunter hive?
我最喜欢的人也有赏金猎人啊
Some of my favorite people are bounty hunters.
也许这个士兵的样本
And perhaps, this specimen of soldier
可能会考虑加入我们的行列
might consider joining our ranks.
我的链码有点问题
Yeah. I've got some clerical concerns regarding my chain code.
如果你同意成为我的执行者
And if you would agree to become my enforcer,
你最不必担心的就是这些繁文缛节
clerical concerns would be the least of your worries.
但是你 我的朋友
But you, my friend,
公会非常欢迎你的回归
you will be welcome back into the Guild with open arms.
走吧 好好享受
So, go off, enjoy yourself.
当你准备好回来的时候
And when you're ready to return,
所有的任务随你挑选
you will have the pick of all quarries.
我手头还有更要紧的事
I'm afraid I have more pressing matters at hand.
照顾好这个小家伙
Take care of this little one.
或许是它照顾你
Or maybe, it'll take care of you.
你拿的是什么
What do you got there?
我以为我再也见不到它了
I didn't think I'd see this again.
你好好保管吧
Why don't you hang onto that?